Now, as you are already aware...
1-1-1's coming!
It's Tawny's birthday!
The number one biggest day of the whole year!
What? That's his birthday?
Wow, stop the presses.
I gotta get him to bangin' his gift, I don't know what to do!
You could start by leaving my checkout line.
That man must have spilled some deets on what he's hoping to get
during one of your little bro chats.
I don't think so.
He's your boyfriend, ask him yourself.
Yamada, you're a boy!
Have you gotten a gift from a girl that made you freak?
Or filled you with all the warm, fuzzy feelsies?
I'm drawing a blank.
Come on, you're asking Yamada?
Him and Tani are like different species.
A photo album?
Ah, cutie!
Wait, he pulls?
Not again.
I had no idea Yamada was so experienced.
It's like a gulf of game has opened up between us.
Taira, how about you?
How about you?
I mean, if you ask me.
I really don't care if my birthday presents are good or bad.
It's more about the fact that someone remembered my birthday.
Knowing someone celebrating you should be enough to make you happy.
Or whatever.
That was mature AF, bruh.
But it's more fun finding out someone's celebrating you when it comes out of left field.
With balloons.
Surprise or bust, huh?
It's his first birthday since we became a thing, so doi!
I'll give him a surprise so good it ruins him for other women and for other birthdays.
Tani's gonna remember this one till he dies.
Is that a threat?
Terrifying.
めがねを外してさあちゃんと目を合わせてよカメラのシャッターを切って恋を閉じ込めてよ
山あり谷ありの恋です 三角に口を尖らして 四角い言葉の角を取って君にハートを贈りたい
サイン、コサイン、タンジェント 心の角度が広がって
電流が走る一目惚れ 覚えていてフレーニング
純度100%の想いも 異心伝心させたいな
君とあたしは正反対 恋はいつも想定外
ねえねえ聞いて 言葉を尽くして君に伝えたいの
心が体に追いついて気づけば目で追ってる
眼鏡を外してさあちゃんと目を合わせてよ
恋は走り出したの?放課後まで待てない
大事な言葉ほど酸素を切らみたい
辞書にないあたしなりの言葉で早く
君に伝えたいのかね
ご視聴ありがとうございました
Nice! Then we should walk home together!
Cool.
Big dub!
We walk home all the time, but it'll be extra special tomorrow!
What do I do?
I feel like she's going to surprise me with something.
Back in middle school...
Happy birthday, Hinaji! We love you!
Thank you, guys! You're like the best friends ever!
It was tradition to celebrate all of our classmates' birthdays.
The thought was, if everyone was celebrated equally, no one would feel left out or sad.
Eventually, it was my turn.
Tawny! We have something to tell you!
Happy birthday, Hinaji!
Thank you.
Oh, that's a different reaction.
I still don't know how I should have responded.
Yay!
This isn't good.
I have no idea how to act surprised.
I haven't stopped messing with you, but you keep giving me all these hilarious reactions!
Ah, yes!
Aw, come on! Really?
Man, I'm beat.
Hey, Taita.
Do you mind if I ask you something?
What?
Is reacting to things a skill you've worked on?
I'm pretty sure that comes with being a human.
Tani!
We're up next! Let's go!
Wait.
Does he know Suzuki's gonna surprise him?
You're right.
Either way, no one knows it's my birthday, and no one would care.
Aw, you guys! Stop! This is so embarrassing!
How pathetic. For a second, I thought those guys were trying to surprise me.
You good, dude? Your face is red.
Bless you. Catch a cold or something?
No, I'm fine. You're just seeing things...
Wow. Gaslight much?
Taito, where's your umbrella?
The rain's not bad. I'd rather deal with some sprinkles than mess with it.
That's some guy logic.
That's thunder.
Let's hurry and get back inside.
Are you freaking kidding me?!
Just put me out of my misery already.
And on your birthday, too. What gives?
Huh? Wait, you knew?
We all said our birthdays in Spanish class, remember? Guess it stuck with me.
Oh, we did?
Yours is El Diez de Octubre.
I remembered because you pronounced it so fancy.
Okay, dude, you know what?
What's the matter? Are you hoping for a big birthday party at lunch?
Hell no, of course not!
I'm only teasing.
Hang on. Got a gift for ya.
This sticker came with the bread I ate for lunch.
Your face is giving I don't want it.
Nah. My hands are just dirty. I'll grab it later.
Thanks, Asuma.
Aww. Hey, cool yeti.
A little cutesy for you, though. I'm surprised.
Huh?
Whoa! Is that the one I gave you on your birthday?
I didn't know you were so scentsy, dude.
Brrrr.
It's late. Should I try to stay up until midnight?
If she does try to call me, I don't want her to think I ignored her.
No, I'm probably being too self-conscious again.
That's fine.
Hello?
Yay! You're still awake! What a relief.
Or were you asleep and I woke you up?
I was awake.
Really? Because you sound like you've been hibernating.
Sorry, I'll be super quick. Just wait a few more seconds, okay?
It's time.
Happy birthday, Tawny.
At first, I was trying to think of a supergiant, over-the-top surprise.
But the more I thought about it, being the first person to wish you happy birthday was what mattered most.
Thank you.
But then I went and woke you up.
I wasn't asleep.
Don't lie on your birthday.
He sounds so cute when he's sleepy.
Okay.
Night-night.
Talk to you later.
I love you.
Too far, too far.
Too far.
How do you tell?
Good morning, Tawny.
How's it hangin', pussy boy?
What?
It's your birthday, Tawny?
Happy birthday.
Hey!
Felicitations nerd, how's about a sticker?
Thank you.
How do you tell?
Good morning Tawny!
How's it hangin', pussy boy?
What?
It's your birthday, Tawny?
Happy birthday!
Felicitations nerd!
How's that a sticker?
Thank you.
there you go gummies oh thank you tawny
thank you sure gotta get to work look at him all embarrassed classic title hey i heard it's
your birthday tawny growing up what grade are you in artist girl what oh that reminds me
hey shifthead how's work huh why are you here i hope you have better birthday plans than this
obvi tawny's birthdaying has only just begun
you're shopping too come again happy belated birthday
huh your birthday was last month but i just found out today you gave me a present so i should give you
one huh azu told us and we're glad she did dude you gotta tell your friends these things
okay we better get going time to get this b-day show on the road so i'm the opening act happy belated bro
i don't know what happened sounded like a party out here no no no party
voila candles and a lighter for the special occasion you're always prepared
come on come on stand straight they might be too chunky for the cake
all right let's get lit
somehow
17 my older and wiser tawny thank you
i'm so happy
i'm so good
do you want to do a quick trade with me okay
this here's for you tawny happy happy birthday
it's a scarf i know it's not quite cold enough yet but if i waited until winter i'd be minimizing my
chances to see you all scarfed up if you wore it i'd be super gagged but no pressure
it's not quite cold enough to see you all
suzuki
wait is he gonna
thank you this was perfect
it's an excellent gift
oh this weekend we should go where you want to go and do what you want to do
what i want to do
yep we're always going where i want to go so you pick
all right i'll think about it huzzah all hail the birthday king
this weekend we should go where you want to go and do what you want to do
what do i want to do the harder i try to think of something the more i feel anything is fine
maybe i should just tell suzuki that or maybe not if you want to we could grab one perfect tour
can i make another shallow request is it possible that i'm way too passive
the last time i was here must have been an elementary
do you come here on the reg no i just remember liking it as a kid
aww adorbs that's really only part of it there's nothing good at the theater right now
i've already been to the zoo that's a bit on the short side
after hours of brain freeze he made a cool decision
do you want to see the special exhibit while we're here
oh let's go seems like a popping place to be oh my god
i can't see squat and there's so much breath
tani tani where'd you go suzuki this way
well that was a bust
at least we got a great view of the back of people's big giant heads
i'm sorry why though you've got nothing to apologize for now let's go
there's a treasure trove of history left to see to the permanent exhibits
the extra space is nice
wow
don't go turn the light
it's not a moth
cute look at its cute stubby legs
there's so much to see oh my god it's us
it's already dark we need a biggish dent it's crazy to think how much there still is we'll have to plan
another visit someday ah i had so much fun
this walk-ins got me starving want to grab a quick dinner
there's supposedly a pretty good restaurant in this area let's go
look at you doing date recon you're so cute
sorry not your fault the world's against us there's another restaurant nearby that we could check out
dang soldier how much recon did you do
jesus well ramen places move kind of quick so maybe it's fine what do you think yeah or nay
another time yeah i don't think we're that bougie
i don't think we're that old food truck hallelujah we're saved
it sure gets chilly when the sun goes down
ah toasty tongue
for some reason none of my plans went the way they were supposed to today
i guess until now i've been depending on her to make all the plans
we walked a lot aren't you getting tired well duh but at the same time it's making this taste more
scrumptious than i dreamed i wish i could have eaten in one of the restaurants you found beforehand
too bad but if you ask me if this place is totally bomb
you're always going along with the things i want to do
so i wanted today to be about you dia del tani but i still ended up having a great time anyway
honestly i enjoy things more when you're having fun suzuki
i don't care where we go or what we do it isn't about that cool places and activities are great but
spending time with you is the part i enjoy the most
uh you're kidding you read my mind what i feel the same way
i'll say things like i want to go there or i'm dying to try this
but really it's always a big fat excuse to spend extra time with my tawny we're total twinsies
wait is that weird no we're alike you're right i mean it when i say this thanks for everything
you do so serious where's all this coming from you goob what that was worrying you for the entire day
i wish i could have done a better job of taking the lead for once everything turned out a-okay
but i appreciate you thinking about it it's kind of funny today was supposed to be all about
continuing tiny super bus and birthday bash but in the end i made you worry about me bus and birthday
what that's not your fault i was spinning in circles for no reason but the museum actually
ended up being a lot of fun all right now i'm all antsy to check out that art museum sometime too
yeah let's i have some interest in european art history
the intellectual aspect is low-key lost on me but i'm ready to grow
you're fine it's the artistic aspect that's lost on me
well i'll see you at school
well
Sweet dreams.
Yeah, you too!
Ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha!
Yay!
Ahh!
My heart!
Oh my, I'm guessing it went well.
Yahoo!
Thank you.
See you next time.